Tom Raymond Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
Tom Raymond collection 1984-2003
AFC 2009/029
Raymond, Tom, 1947-
2 manuscript folders.
12,437 photographs: color and black-and-white transparencies, slides, negatives; various sizes.
14 linear feet.
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of photographs taken by Tom Raymond documenting storytellers and audiences at the annual National Storytelling Festival, Jonesborough, Tennessee, from circa 1984 to 2003. Most are 35 mm color slides and negatives. The collection documents the major storytellers and performers at the festival with more than 1,500 photographs of storyteller Ray Hicks taken at the festival over the years and at his home in Beech Mountain, North Carolina.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Aaron, Moses, 1944-; Aoki, Brenda Wong.; Armstrong, Jennifer (Musician); Ball, Patrick.; Barton, Bob, 1939-; Basinger, John.; Beekman, Jeannine Pasini.; Bias-Insignares, Harriette.; Birch, Carol (Carol L.); Black, Judith.; Bloch, Muriel, 1954-; Bok, Gordon.; Brother Blue.; Bruchac, Joseph, 1942-; Brummett, Curt.; Burch, Mildred.; Cabral, Len.; Campbell, John, 1933-2006.; Cotter, Michael, 1931-; Creed, Robert Payson, 1925-; Davis, Donald, 1944-; Deedy, Carmen Agra.; Del Negro, Janice.; Del Seamonds, Leeny.; DeSpain, Pleasant.; Ducey, Gay.; Elliott, Douglas B.; Ellis, Elizabeth, 1943-; Ellis, Rex M., 1951-; Ferlatte, Diane.; Flodin, Lucinda.; Forest, Heather.; Frederick, Dennis, 1950-2005.; Freeman, Barbara, 1944-; Gillman, Jackson, 1954-; Gore, Al, 1948-; Goss, Linda.; Graham, Len.; Grear, Joyce.; Hamilton, Mary, 1952-; Harley, Bill, 1954-; Hayes, Joe.; Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003.; Holloway, Martha.; Holt, David, 1946-; Horner, Beth.; Izard, Anne.; Jojo, Kala.; Jones, Francis Firebrace.; Juditz, Vicki.; Keding, Dan.; Kikuchi-Yngojo, Robert.; Klein, Susan, 1951-; Koram, Jamal.; Larkin, Chuck, 1931-; Lenihan, Edmund.; Lepp, Bil, 1970-; Lieberman, Syd, 1944-; Lipman, Doug.; Lloyd, Angela, 1954-; Locke, Kevin.; Loya, Olga.; Lupton, Hugh.; May, Jim, 1947-; McBride-Smith, Barbara, 1944-; McConnell, Doc.; McCutcheon, John, 1952-; McGill, Alice.; Mitchell, Waddie, 1950-; Mooney, William.; Moses, Johnny.; Norfolk, Bobby, 1951-; Novak, David.; Nwanga, Namu.; O'Callahan, Jay.; O'Halloran, Susan.; O'Neal, John, 1940-2019.; Orunamamu.; Parent, Michael.; Pennington, Lee.; Phillips, Utah.; Pinkerton, J. G. "Paw Paw", 1926-2008.; Ramsey, Buck.; Raymond, Tom, 1947-; Regan-Blake, Connie, 1947-; Reneaux, J. J., 1955-; Rogers, Gamble.; Rogers, Sally, 1954-; Ross, Gayle.; Rubright, Lynn, 1936-; Sanfield, Steve.; Schimmel, Nancy.; Schram, Peninnah.; Seeger, Pete, 1919-2014.; Simms, Laura.; Smith, Jimmy Neil.; Smith, Mary Carter.; Spelman, Jon, 1942-; Stivender, Ed, 1946-; Taylor, Rangimoana.; Teare, Billy.; Thomas, Taffy.; Thomason, Dovie.; Timpanelli, Gloria.; Torrence, Jackie.; Umolu, Mary H. (Mary Harden); Watkins, Kel.; Weakley, Tom.; Weir, Liz.; Wilson, Madafo Lloyd.; Windham, Kathryn Tucker.; Zarzyski, Paul.
Organizations
Eth-Noh-Tec (Performing group); International Storytelling Center; National Storytelling Festival.; Storycrafters.; Storyweavers.; Taifa (Performing group)
Subjects
Folk festivals--Tennessee--Jonesborough.; Storytellers--United States--Photographs.; Storytelling festivals--Tennessee--Jonesborough.
Places
Jonesborough (Tenn.)
Titles
Photographs of the annual National Storytelling Festival, 1984-2012
Form/Genre
Color slides.; Contact sheets.; Digital photographs.; Documentary photography.; Film negatives.; Film transparencies.; Photographic prints.
Arrangement
Organized by subject and then by format into the following Series: I. Manuscripts; II. Storytellers Performances; III. Various Storytellers; IV. Events.
Acquisition
Tom Raymond donated the collection to the American Folklife Center in 2009.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Related Materials
The International Storytelling Collection (AFC 2001/008) has manuscript, sound, graphic and visual documentation related to this collection.
Tom Raymond's early 1980s photographs of the National Storytelling Festival are included in the American Folklife Center's International Storytelling Collection (AFC 2001/008).
Access and Restrictions
Collection is open for research; access to collection materials may be restricted. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Bibliography
Images of the storytellers pictured this collection can be found in Tom Raymond's book, Timeless voices: Images of the International Storytelling Festival. International Storytelling Press of the International Storytelling Association, 1997.
Collection Concordance by Format
Manuscripts
2 Folders Box 1
Graphic Materials
10,608 Color slides Box 1-9, 12-13
1,243 Color reversals Box 10-11, 14
429 Negatives Box 10-11, 14
103 Photographic Prints Box 15
54 Contact sheets Box 15
Biographical History
Tom Raymond, the official photographer for the International Storytelling Festival from 1980-2009, began working with the International Storytelling Center, formerly known as the National Association for the Preservation and Perpetuation of Storytelling (NAPPS), beginning in circa 1980. In 1983, Raymond established Fresh Air Photo, a commercial photography and post production studio based in Johnson City, Tennessee.
Raymond first pursued a medical career. He earned a B.S. at the University of Tennessee in Knoxville. He later obtained his M.S. at East Carolina University in Greenville, North Carolina, and a Ph.D. in biological science at the Bowman Gary School of Medicine at Wake Forest University in Winston-Salem. Three postdoctoral positions followed at the University of Iowa, the University of Oregon Health Sciences Center, and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. In 1978, Raymond joined the faculty of the Department of Internal Medicine at East Tennessee State University.
Raymond's career in photography began as an undergraduate at the University of Tennessee (UT) while he was working for The Daily Beacon, a student publication. He earned several awards for photojournalism while at UT, but photography was put on hold while he pursued a career in academic medicine. Having published more than 60 peer-reviewed articles in scientific journals and presented his research at meetings throughout the United States and abroad, he resigned from UT in 1987 to pursue photography full-time as the owner of Fresh Air Photo.
Scope and Content
The Tom Raymond Collection documents the performances of international and national storytellers at the International Storytelling Festival in Jonesborough, Tennessee. The collection primarily consists of graphic images which span 20 years, 1983-2003. Raymond's photographs of International storyteling performances prior to 1983 are found in the International Storytelling Collection (AFC 2001/008).
The bulk of the collection contains color slides, but also includes negatives, color reversal film, contact sheets and photographic prints. The images mainly capture the on-stage performances of the featured tellers but also capture the storytellers on the grounds of the festival as well as publicity photographs of storytellers.
Of note in the collection are Raymond’s 1500 photos of Appalachian storyteller Ray Hicks from Beech Mountain, North Carolina. Also in the collection is Raymond's documentation of Hicks' Home Going Service when he passed away in 2003.
Container List
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - Finding aid (Box-folder 1/1)
  - 28th Annual International Storytelling Festival Program of Events (Box-folder 1/2)
- Series II: Photographs of Storyteller Performances
  The International Storytelling Festival unless otherwise noted, 1983-2003
  - Color slides
    - Aaron, Moses, MA:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 1/3)
      Moses Aaron, Australian storyteller, onstage. 6 color slides.
    - African Women: Orunamamu and Umolu, Mary H., AW:PH1-PH73 (Box-folder 1/4)
      Orunamamu (Mary Beth Washington) and Mary Umolu, performing at Swappin’ Ground. 73 35mm color slides. (1 business card of Mary H. Umolu, Ph.D.).
    - Aoki, Brenda Wong, BWA:PH1-PH79 (Box-folder 1/5)
      Brenda Wong Aoki, Asian-American storyteller, onstage. 79 35mm color slides.
    - Armstrong, Jennifer, JA:PH1-PH47 (Box-folder 1/6)
      Jennifer Armstrong offstage on the grounds. 47 35mm color slides.
    - Ball, Patrick, PB:PH1-PH51 (Box-folder 1/7)
      Patrick Ball, California-born Celtic harpist and storyteller, onstage and offstage on the grounds. 51 35mm color slides.
    - Barton, Bob, BB:PH1 (Box-folder 1/8)
      Bob Barton, Canadian storyteller, in candid shot on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Basinger, John, JB:PH1 (Box-folder 1/9)
      John Basinger, Connecticut storyteller and professor emeritus of theater and sign at Three River Community College, offstage on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Beekman, Jeannine Pasini, JPB:PH1-PH48 (Box-folder 1/10)
      Jeannine Pasini Beekman, Louisiana storyteller, onstage. 48 35mm color slides.
    - Bias-Insignares, Harriette, HAI:PH1-PH5 (Box-folder 1/11)
      Harriette Bias-Insignares along with Jackie Torrence offstage on the grounds. 5 35mm color slides.
    - Birch, Carol, CB:PH1-PH66 (Box-folder 1/12)
      Carol Birch onstage and offstage on the grounds. 66 35mm color slides.
    - Black, Judith, JB:PH1-PH128 (Box-folder 1/13)
      Judith Black, Pittsburgh-born storyteller, onstage and at the Ghost Stories segment. 128 35mm color slides.
    - Bloch, Muriel, MB:PH1 (Box-folder 1/14)
      Muriel Bloch, French storyteller, offstage on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Bok, Gordon, GB:PH1-PH2 (Box-folder 1/15)
      Gordon Bok, a native of Maine, onstage. 2 35mm color slides.
    - Brother Blue (1/2), BB:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 1/16)
      Brother Blue street performer, actor and musician performing at Swappin’ Ground and on Main Street, Jonesborough, Tennessee. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Brother Blue (2/2), BB:PH201-PH232 (Box-folder 1/17)
      32 35mm color slides and 1 business card.
    - Bruchac, Joseph, JB:PH01-PH42 (Box-folder 1/18)
      Joseph Bruchac, from the Adirondack mountain foothills, onstage and offstage on the grounds. 42 35mm color slides.
    - Brummett, Curt, CB:PH01-PH29 (Box-folder 1/19)
      Curt Brummett, cowboy storyteller from Clovis, New Mexico, onstage. 29 35mm color slides.
    - Burch, Milbre, MB:PH01-PH88 (Box-folder 1/20)
      Milbre Burch, a native of Atlanta, Georgia, onstage and offstage on the grounds. 88 35mm color slides.
    - Cabral, Len, LC:PH1-PH75 (Box-folder 1/21)
      Len Cabral, of Cape Verdean ancestry, onstage and offstage on the grounds. 75 35mm color slides.
    - Campbell, John and Len Graham, CG:PH1-PH62 (Box-folder 2/22)
      John Campbell and Len Graham, an Irish duo onstage. 62 35mm color slides.
    - Cotter, Michael, MC:PH1-PH35 (Box-folder 2/23)
      Michael Cotter, third generation farmer, onstage. 35 35mm color slides.
    - Creed, Robert Payson, RPC:PH1 (Box-folder 2/24)
      Robert Creed offstage on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Davis, Donald (1/3), DD:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 2/25)
      Donald Davis, retired minister from southern Appalachia, onstage. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Davis, Donald (2/3), DD:PH201-PH400 (Box-folder 2/26)
      200 35mm color slides.
    - Davis, Donald (3/3), DD:PH401-PH572 (Box-folder 2/27)
      172 35mm color slides.
    - Deedy, Carmen Agra, CD:PH1-PH119 (Box-folder 2/28)
      Carmen Deedy, Cuban-born, onstage. 119 35mm color slides.
    - Del Negro, Janice, JDN:PH1-PH10 (Box-folder 2/29)
      Janice Del Negro, New York-born, onstage. 10 35mm color slides.
    - Del Seamonds, Leeny, LDS:PH1-PH10 (Box-folder 2/30)
      Leeny Del Seamonds, Philadelphia-born, onstage. 10 35mm color slides.
    - DeSpain, Pleasant, PDS:PH1 (Box-folder 2/31)
      Pleasant DeSpain offstage on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Ducey, Gay, GD:PH1-PH51 (Box-folder 2/32)
      Gay Ducey, children's librarian in Oakland, California, onstage. 51 35mm color slides.
    - Elliott, Doug B., DE:PH1-PH81 (Box-folder 2/33)
      Doug Elliot onstage and offstage on the grounds. 81 35mm color slides
    - Ellis, Austin H, AE:PH1-PH62 (Box-folder 2/34)
      Austin Ellis performing at Swappin’ Ground. 62 35mm color slides.
    - Ellis, Elizabeth, EE:PH01-PH03 (Box-folder 2/35)
      Elizabeth Ellis onstage and offstage on the grounds. 3 35mm color slides.
    - Ellis, Rex, RE:PH01-PH180 (Box-folder 2/36)
      Rex Ellis onstage and at Swappin' Ground. 80 35mm color slides.
    - Eth-Noh-Tec (1/2), ENT:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 3/37)
      Eth-Noh-Tec (Nancy Wang and Robert Kikuchi-Yngojo) signing autographs and onstage. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Eth-Noh-Tec (2/2), ENT:PH201-PH274 (Box-folder 3/38)
      Eth-Noh-Tec (Nancy Wang and Robert Kikuchi-Yngojo) onstage. 74 35mm color slides.
    - Ferlatte, Diane, DF:PH1-PH4 (Box-folder 3/39)
      Diane Ferlatte offstage performance and candid shots on the grounds. 4 35mm color slides.
    - Forest, Heather, HF:PH1-PH40 (Box-folder 3/40)
      Heather Forest onstage. 40 35mm color slides.
    - Freeman, Barbara, BF:PH1-PH7 (Box-folder 3/41)
      Barbara Freeman onstage and offstage on the grounds. 7 35mm color slides.
    - Gillenwater-McConnell, Hannah, HG:PH1 (Box-folder 3/42)
      Hannah Gillenwater-McConnell offstage on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide
    - Gillman, Jackson, 1954, JG:PH1 (Box-folder 3/43)
      Jackson Gillman offstage on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Goss, Linda, LG:PH1 (Box-folder 3/44)
      Linda Goss offstage on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Grear, Joyce, JG:PH1-PH195 (Box-folder 3/45)
      Joyce Grear onstage and at Swappin’ Ground. 195 35mm color slides.
    - Hamilton, Mary, MH:PH1 (Box-folder 3/46)
      Mary Hamilton offstage on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Harley, Bill, 1954, BH:PH1-PH77 (Box-folder 3/47)
      Bill Harley onstage. 77 35mm color slides.
    - Hayes, Joe, JH:PH1 (Box-folder 3/48)
      Joe Hayes offstage on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003 (1/9), RH:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 3/49)
      Ray Hicks onstage and offstage on the grounds. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003 (2/9), RH:PH201-PH400 (Box-folder 3/50)
      Ray Hicks onstage, offstage on the grounds and at Swappin’ Ground. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003 (3/9), RH:PH401-PH600 (Box-folder 3/51)
      Ray Hicks onstage solo, onstage with his wife Rosa, performing at Swappin’ Ground and in candid shots on the grounds. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003 (4/9), RH:PH601-PH800 (Box-folder 4/52)
      Ray Hicks onstage, at Swappin’ Ground, at The Log Cabin, including being interviewed and pictured among Festival goers on the grounds. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003 (5/9), RH:PH801-PH1000 (Box-folder 4/53)
      Ray Hicks onstage, at Swappin’ Ground and at The Log Cabin. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003 (6/9), RH:PH1001-PH1200 (Box-folder 4/54)
      Ray Hicks onstage, signing autographs, performing at Doc McConnell’s Old Medicine wagon and at Swappin’ Ground. The Hicks family is also pictured performing on the grounds. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003 (7/9), RH: PH1201-PH1358 (Box-folder 4/55)
      Ray and Rosa Hicks onstage and Rosa Hicks in candid shots on the grounds. 158 35mm color slides.
    - Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003 (8/9), RH: PH1359-PH1499 (Box-folder 4/56)
      Ray Hicks at his home in Beech Mountain, North Carolina, October 2000. 141 35mm color slides.
    - Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003 (9/9), RH: PH1500-PH1514 (Box-folder 4/57)
      Tribute to Ray Hicks with Rosa Hicks, Connie Regan Blake and others inside a Festival Tent. 15 35mm color slides.
    - Holloway, Martha, MH:PH1-PH28 (Box-folder 4/58)
      Martha Holloway performing offstage. 28 35mm color slides.
    - Holt, David, DH:PH1-PH95 (Box-folder 4/59)
      David Holt onstage and offstage on the grounds. 95 35mm color slides.
    - Horner, Beth, BH:PH1-PH18 (Box-folder 4/60)
      Beth Horner onstage. 18 35mm color slides.
    - Izard, Anne, AI:PH1-PH4 (Box-folder 4/61)
      Anne Izard onstage. 4 35mm color slides.
    - Jenkins, Robert "Bob", RJ:PH1-PH20 (Box-folder 4/62)
      Robert "Bob" Jenkins onstage and offstage on the grounds. 20 35mm color slides.
    - Jojo, Kala, KJ:PH1-PH50 (Box-folder 4/63)
      Kala Jojo onstage. 50 35mm color slides.
    - Jones, Francis Firebrace, FF:PH1-PH8 (Box-folder 4/64)
      Francis Firebrace Jones onstage. 8 35mm color slides.
    - Juditz, Vicki, VJ:PH1-PH22 (Box-folder 5/65)
      Vicki Juditz onstage. 22 35mm color slides.
    - Keding, Dan, DK:PH1-PH19 (Box-folder 5/66)
      Dan Keding onstage. 19 35mm color slides.
    - Klein, Susan, SK:PH1-PH10 (Box-folder 5/67)
      Susan Klein onstage and interacting with crowds inside a festival tent and on the grounds. 10 35mm color slides.
    - Koram, Baba Jamal, ΒJK:PH1-PH66 (Box-folder 5/68)
      Baba Jamal Koram onstage. 66 35mm color slides.
    - Larkin, Chuck, CL:PH1-PH10 (Box-folder 5/69)
      Chuck Larkin onstage, interacting with the crowd and in candid shots on the grounds. 10 35mm color slides.
    - Lenihan, Edmund (Eddie), EL:PH1 (Box-folder 5/70)
      Eddie Lenihan in candid shot on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Lepp, Bill, BL:PH1-PH13 (Box-folder 5/71)
      Bill Lepp performing onstage and interacting with crowds on the grounds. 133 35mm color slides.
    - Lieberman, Syd, SL:PH1-PH104 (Box-folder 5/72)
      Syd Lieberman onstage. 104 35mm color slides.
    - Lipman, Doug, DL:PH1 (Box-folder 5/73)
      Doug Lipman in candid shot on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Lloyd, Angela, AL:PH1-PH45 (Box-folder 5/74)
      Angela Lloyd performing onstage and offstage on the grounds. 45 35mm color slides.
    - Locke, Kevin, KL:PH1-PH25 (Box-folder 5/75)
      Kevin Locke onstage. 25 35mm color slides.
    - Loya, Olga, OL:PH1-PH40 (Box-folder 5/76)
      Olga Loya onstage. 40 35mm color slides.
    - Lupton, Hugh, HL:PH1-PH13 (Box-folder 5/77)
      Hugh Lupton onstage. 13 35mm color slides.
    - Lwanga, Namu, NL:PH1-PH95 (Box-folder 5/78)
      Namu Lwanga along with audience participation onstage. 63 35mm color slides.
    - May, Jim, 1947-, JM:PH1-PH19 (Box-folder 5/79)
      Jim May performing onstage and offstage on the grounds. 19 35mm color slides.
    - McBride-Smith, Barbara, BMS:PH1-PH104 (Box-folder 5/80)
      Barbara McBride-Smith onstage. 104 35mm color slides.
    - McConnell, Doc (1\2), DM:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 5/81)
      Doc McConnell onstage, at the “Old Medicine Show” and at the Swappin’ Ground. 200 color slides.
    - McConnell, Doc (2\2), DM:PH201-PH357 (Box-folder 5/82)
      Doc McConnell performing at the “Old Medicine Show,” the Swappin’ Ground, and on the grounds interacting with the crowd and signing autographs. 157 color slides.
    - McCutcheon, John, JMC:PH1-PH20 (Box-folder 5/83)
      John McCutcheon onstage. 20 color slides.
    - McGill, Alice, AMG:PH1 (Box-folder 6/84)
      Alice McGill in candid shot on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Mitchell, Dennis, DM:PH1-PH33 (Box-folder 6/85)
      Dennis Mitchell performing at Swappin’ Ground. 33 35mm color slides
    - Mitchell, Waddie, WM:PH1-PH85 (Box-folder 6/86)
      Waddie Mitchell onstage, Swappin’ Ground and in candid shots on the grounds. 85 35mm color slides.
    - Mooney William, BM:PH1-PH17 (Box-folder 6/87)
      Bill Mooney onstage. 17 35mm color slides.
    - Moses, Johnny, JM:PH1-PH42 (Box-folder 6/88)
      Johnny Moses onstage, interacting with the audience and in candid shots on the grounds. 42 35mm color slides.
    - Norfolk, Bobby, BN:PH1-PH18 (Box-folder 6/89)
      Bobby Norfolk onstage, performing offstage and in candid shots on the grounds. 18 35mm color slides.
    - Novak, David, DN:PH1-PH44 (Box-folder 6/90)
      David Novak onstage. 44 35mm color slides.
    - O’Callahan, Jay (1/3), JO:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 6/91)
      Jay O’Callahan onstage, at Doc McConnell’s "Old Medicine Show," interacting with crowds and in candid shots on the grounds. 200 35mm color slides.
    - O’Callahan, Jay (2/3), JO:PH201-PH400 (Box-folder 6/92)
      Jay O’Callahan onstage interacting with crowds. 200 35mm color slides.
    - O’Callahan, Jay (3/3), JO:PH401-403 (Box-folder 6/93)
      Jay O’Callahan onstage and in candid shots on the grounds. 3 35mm color slides.
    - O’Halloran, Susan, SO:PH1-PH8 (Box-folder 6/94)
      Susan O’Halloran onstage. 8 35mm color slides.
    - O’Neal, John, 1940- (Jones, Junebug Jabbo), JO:PH1-PH19 (Box-folder 6/95)
      John O'Neal, (Junebug Jabbo) onstage. 19 35mm color slides.
    - Parent, Michael, MP:PH1-PH7 (Box-folder 6/96)
      Michael Parent onstage and in candid shots on the grounds. 7 35mm color slides.
    - Parker, Michael "Mac", MMP:PH1-PH25 (Box-folder 6/97)
      Mac Parker onstage. 25 35mm color slides.
    - Pierce, Maggie, MKP:PH1-PH5 (Box-folder 6/98)
      Maggie Pierce onstage. 5 35mm color slides.
    - Pennington, Lee, LP:PH1-PH25 (Box-folder 6/99)
      Lee Pennington onstage and in candid shots on the grounds. 25 35mm color slides.
    - Phillips, Utah, UP:PH1 (Box-folder 6/100)
      Utah Phillips in candid shot on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Pinkerton, J.G. “Paw Paw”, MKP:PH1-PH5 (Box-folder 6/101)
      J. G. "Paw Paw" Pinkerton onstage. 15 35mm color slides.
    - Portman, June, JP:PH1-PH35 (Box-folder 6/102)
      June Portman onstage. 35 35mm color slides.
    - Ramsey, Buck, BR:PH1-PH5 (Box-folder 6/103)
      Buck Ramsey onstage. 5 35mm color slides.
    - Regan-Blake, Connie (1/3), CR-B:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 6/104)
      Connie Regan-Blake is half of the storytelling duo team of the Folktellers, who resides in North Carolina. Her stories range from hilarious traditional Appalachian Mountain tales to poignant true-life drama. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Regan-Blake, Connie (2/3), CR-B:PH201-PH400 (Box-folder 6/105)
    - Regan-Blake, Connie (3/3), CR-B:PH401-PH449 (Box-folder 7/106)
      49 35mm color slides.
    - Reneaux, J. J., JJR:PH1-PH41 (Box-folder 7/107)
      J. J. Reneaux onstage and in candid shots on the grounds. 41 35mm color slides.
    - Roadside Theatre (Organization: Washington, D.C.), RT:PH1-PH13 (Box-folder 7/108)
      Roadside Theatre company onstage. 13 35mm color slides.
    - Rocha, Antonio, AR:PH1-PH71 (Box-folder 7/109)
      Antonio Rocha onstage. 71 35mm color slides.
    - Rogers, Gamble, JGR:PH1-PH75 (Box-folder 7/110)
      Gamble Rogers, native of Florida and teller of philosophical humor performing onstage. 75 35mm color slides.
    - Rogers, Sally, SR:PH1-PH30 (Box-folder 7/111)
      Sally Rogers onstage and in candid shots. 30 35mm color slides.
    - Ross, Gayle, GR:PH1-PH33 (Box-folder 7/112)
      Gayle Ross onstage, signing autographs and in candid shots on the grounds. 33 35mm color slides.
    - Rubright, Lynn, LR:PH1-PH94 (Box-folder 7/113)
      Lynn Rubright onstage. 94 35mm color slides.
    - Sacre, Antonio, AS:PH1-PH10 (Box-folder 7/114)
      Antonio Sacre onstage. 10 35mm color slides.
    - Sanfield, Steve, SS:PH1-PH27 (Box-folder 7/115)
      Steve Sanfield onstage and in candid shots on the grounds. 27 35mm color slides.
    - Schimmel, Nancy, NS:PH1 (Box-folder 7/116)
      Nancy Schimmel in candid shot on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide.
    - Schram, Penninah, PS:PH1-PH22 (Box-folder 7/117)
      Penninah Schram onstage. 22 35mm color slides
    - Sea Island Singers (Georgia Sea Island Singers), GSIS:PH1-PH63 (Box-folder 7/118)